<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>creikey</title>
    <link>https://creikey.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on creikey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:25:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://creikey.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Production</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/projects/musicproduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/projects/musicproduction/</guid>
      <description>I use lmms to create music for games and personal use. My soundcloud is here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/projects/modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/projects/modeling/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy using blender to 3d model various objects and to make VFX. I also use blender to develop assets for game development. My blendswap profile is here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/projects/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/projects/programming/</guid>
      <description>I am continually trying to improve my skills as a programmer, with the goal of being able to create and do anything I want as efficiently as possible with a computer. Most of my projects are either on my github or on my personal git server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Development</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/projects/gamedevelopment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 02:19:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/projects/gamedevelopment/</guid>
      <description>My primary engine of choice for game development is Godot, for a multitude of reasons. I have a club at La Jolla High School called Viking Games, where we develop games to earn money towards our ASB. All of my personal games can be seen here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Jam Fail</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/blog/weekly-jam-fail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 11:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/blog/weekly-jam-fail/</guid>
      <description>Synopsys Sadly, my project idea for week 52 proved to be too much work to be done by one person in the allotted time.
Game idea Orinally the game was supposed to be like this:
 A deserty theme Main shop area with ~4 NPCS 3 bosses Combat top down, shooting style A shop where you could buy weapons  But here&amp;rsquo;s all I was able to get done:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Game Jam Beginning</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/blog/weekly-game-jam-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 22:28:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/blog/weekly-game-jam-beginning/</guid>
      <description>More info about the weekly game jam here
 Hello blog readers! Today marks the offical end of the first day in my participation in the Weekly Game Jam, a weekly competition where game developers from all around collectively develop on a theme for a small prize. The theme for this weeks game jam was
Boss Rush When I saw this theme, nothing came to me at first. I even attempted at collaborating with somebody else, but our attempts at coming up with something different fell short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Website</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/blog/setting-up-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 01:54:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/blog/setting-up-website/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Using hugo to create a website is very easy, as shown in these steps
I followed the hugo quick start guide
And the introduction theme&amp;rsquo;s instructions
Steps Installing hugo Because arch linux has a wide breadth of supported programs in it&amp;rsquo;s repos, I was able to simply run:
sudo pacman -S hugo
And use the hugo new site website command to create the website in a folder named website/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>I respond to email within two days</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://creikey.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:36:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creikey.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> I am a programmer, 3d artist, musician, and game designer
Lightning Round Qualifications  Life scout Competent in C++, C, Golang, Godot, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Java, Vim Able to do 3D design and creation in blender Author of various games on itch.io Over sixty github projects Various musical projects on soundcloud  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>